{
	"records":[
		{
			"question":"2 x 4 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"6 ÷ 2 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"42 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 5 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"72 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"9 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"12 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"10 ÷ 2 =",
			"answer":5
		},
		{
			"question":"108 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"24 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 4 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 6 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"35 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 7 =",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 3 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 2 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"64 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 7 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"32 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 5 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"36 ÷ 12 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"96 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"49 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 6 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"36 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"10 ÷ 10 =",
			"answer":1
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 4 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"28 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 1 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"84 ÷ 12 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"42 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"54 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 12 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"25 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":5
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 10 =",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"12 x 9 =",
			"answer":108
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 8 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"18 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 3 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 7 =",
			"answer":63
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 9 =",
			"answer":72
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 4 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 5 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 6 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"40 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"32 ÷ 4 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 4 =",
			"answer":32
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 8 =",
			"answer":56
		},
		{
			"question":"12 x 4 =",
			"answer":48
		},
		{
			"question":"11 x 6 =",
			"answer":66
		},
		{
			"question":"48 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 9 =",
			"answer":27
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 8 =",
			"answer":64
		},
		{
			"question":"6 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"27 ÷ 3 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 4 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 8 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 12 =",
			"answer":72
		},
		{
			"question":"12 x 9 =",
			"answer":108
		},
		{
			"question":"8 ÷ 2 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"35 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":7
		},
		{
			"question":"64 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 3 =",
			"answer":27
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 9 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 3 =",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 4 =",
			"answer":28
		},
		{
			"question":"9 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":1
		},
		{
			"question":"56 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 3 =",
			"answer":21
		},
		{
			"question":"10 ÷ 5 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"44 ÷ 4 =",
			"answer":11
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 9 =",
			"answer":72
		},
		{
			"question":"12 x 2 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"36 ÷ 9 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 3 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 6 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 9 =",
			"answer":36
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"18 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":3
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 1 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"70 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 8 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"6 x 7 =",
			"answer":42
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 9 =",
			"answer":63
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 5 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 6 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"9 x 8 =",
			"answer":72
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 8 =",
			"answer":24
		},
		{
			"question":"12 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"96 ÷ 8 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 5 =",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"63 ÷ 7 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"72 ÷ 6 =",
			"answer":12
		}
	]
}